https://soulmediccentral.com/webchat/terms?w_t=dwBlAGIAYwBoAGEAdAB8AFIARQBNAEUARABZAEwASQBWAEUAfAAtADEAfAAtADEAfAAtADEAfAB8ADEANAA0ADQANAA3ADgANwA0ADYAMAA0ADgA

SoulMedicCentral.comWhat This Privacy Policy CoversThis privacy policy relates to use of www.soulmediccentral.com, the short code 494949, and virtual webinar experiences done via www.soulmediccentral.com. Standard messaging and data rates may apply.This privacy policy covers how www.soulmediccentral.com and the short code 494949 (hereafter named ‘we’) are the same service provided by SoulMedic Media Group, Inc. and how we will treat the personal information that we collect.Personal information is your information and includes identifiers like your name, address, zip code, city, state, email address, phone number, mobile number, gender, and age. Virtual webinar experiences do not collect personal information unless a user submits their email due to a prize giveaway.By registering a user account with www.soulmediccentral.com or short code 494949 you agree to subscribe to regular email publications or text messages we distribute with the option to unsubscribe or opt out. We will not share your email or mobile phone number with others. All emails or text messages from us will be SoulMedic Media Group, Inc. sponsored initiatives. Standard messaging and data rates may apply.Children under 13 are not permitted to use the www.soulmediccentral.com or short code 494949 service, including chat interaction, and so this privacy policy makes no provision for children’s use of the site.Changes to this Privacy PolicyWe may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information we will send a notice to the primary email address or mobile number specified in your SoulMedicCentral.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.By agreeing to the privacy policy you agree with the mission of SoulMedic Media Inc., the owner of SoulMedicCentral.com.By agreeing to this privacy policy, you also agree that at any time you choose to provide chat information or profile content which suggests you might do harm to yourself or another, SoulMedicCentral.com reserves the right to intervene with local authorities in your area to provide safety to you and/or others. We reserve the right to refuse service if we feel you are in danger to yourself/others and need help beyond what we can provide as a compassion-based chat center.We ask that you refrain from cruel statements in the chat and treat others with kindness. If you choose to not respond positively to the warnings of the SoulMedicCentral.com Staff, your profile and IP address will be blocked.TermsYou must be 13 years and older to use this site, with the exception of the virtual webinar experiences which do not collect any identifiable information of the user.You are responsible for any activity that occurs under your screen name.You are responsible for keeping your password secure.You must not abuse, harass, threaten, impersonate or intimidate other SoulMedicCentral.com users.You may not use the SoulMedicCentral.com service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose. International users agree to comply with all local laws regarding online conduct and acceptable content.You are solely responsible for your conduct and any data, text, information, screen names, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips, links (‘Content’) that you submit, post, and display on the SoulMedicCentral.com service or mobile applications.SoulMedicCentral.com is intended for personal use, not a business solution. Professional or corporate uses of SoulMedicCentral.com are not permitted without our prior written consent.You must not modify, adapt or hack SoulMedicCentral.com, or modify another website so as to state or imply that it is associated with SoulMedicCentral.com.You must not create or submit unwanted email to any SoulMedicCentral.com or its members (‘Spam’).You must not transmit any worms or viruses or any code of a destructive nature.You must not, in the use of SoulMedicCentral.com, violate any laws in your jurisdiction (including but not limited to copyright laws), or to infringe the rights of any third party, including intellectual property rights.Any loss of, or damage to, data is not the responsibility of SoulMedicCentral.com. Use of this service is at your own risk.If at any time you choose to provide chat information or profile content that suggests you might do harm to yourself or another, SoulMedicCentral.com reserves the right to contact authorities, including local authorities in your area to provide safety to you and/or others. You agree that we, in our sole discretion, may use, share, and/or communicate any and all personal information that you have provided or that we possess for the purpose of attempting to secure your health or safety or the health or safety of others.You affirm that you are 13 years of age, or older, as SoulMedicCentral.com is not intended for children under 13.You affirm that you will not create multiple accounts using multiple email addresses and/or phone numbers. Failure to abide by these terms may result in the termination of all accounts.SoulMedicCentral.com is not a professional counseling organization. SoulMedics are not licensed therapists or counselors. The views and chat opinions of the SoulMedics are not necessarily the views and philosophies of SoulMedicCentral.com or the parent organization, SoulMedic Media Group Inc. Our desire is to chat with those that come to us, and through listening, love all people through God’s love.Violation of any of these terms and conditions will result in the termination of your SoulMedicCentral.com account. While SoulMedicCentral.com prohibits such conduct and content on its site, you understand and agree that SoulMedicCentral.com cannot be responsible for the content posted on its web site and, despite our best efforts, you may be exposed to concepts, content, or material that offends you. Use the SoulMedicCentral.com service at your own risk.General ConditionsWe reserve the right to modify or terminate the SoulMedicCentral.com service for any reason, without notice at any time.We reserve the right to alter these Terms of Use at any time. If the alterations constitute a material change to the Terms of Use, we will notify you via an appropriate method. What is a ‘material change’ is at our discretion.We reserve the right to share information with local authorities as well as legal guardians if required documentation is provided.We reserve the right to refuse service to anyone for any reason at any time.CopyrightWe claim no intellectual property rights over any material you provide to the SoulMedicCentral.com service. Otherwise, all content on the SoulMediCentral.com website is copyrighted and may be used only with our prior written permission.If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us at (260) 422-1958.Last updated: 5/5/2020
